findrentals.com 2016-03-15

# Customer Privacy Policy | Find Rentals

The FindRentals.com Customer Privacy Policy has been developed as an extension of our commitment to combine the finest quality products and services with the highest level of integrity in dealing with our customers. The Policy guides how we collect, store and use information about customers and prospects, and it will be periodically assessed against new technologies, business practices and our customers' changing needs. The FindRentals.com site may, from time to time, modify this Customer Privacy Policy to reflect legal, technological and other developments. In that event the changes will appear at this location. Our Policy recognizes two kinds of personal data that deserve varying levels of protection. Personally-Identifiable Information includes, for example, e-mail addresses, billing information, employment status and "click stream" data that tracks user activity on a Web site or online service. FindRentals.com is committed to using all reasonable efforts to abide by the following Policy statement: 

**Collection.**

Personally-Identifiable Information will only be collected to the extent that FindRentals.com deems reasonably necessary to serve a legitimate business purpose. Please be aware that if you disclose Personally-Identifiable Information on Website, that information may be collected and used by third parties without our knowledge and may result in unsolicited communications from third parties. Such activities are beyond the control of FindRentals.com.

**Security.**

Appropriate safeguards will be implemented to ensure the security, integrity and privacy of Personally-Identifiable Information about our customers and prospects. 

**Access.**

Review and correction. Procedures have been developed through which customers and prospects can, upon request, review and correct the Personally-Identifiable Information that has been collected from them by FindRentals.com. These procedures may not, however, compromise the security, integrity and privacy of either FindRentals.com own proprietary databases or databases licensed from third party companies.

**DoubleClick DART Cookie.**  
Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on FindRentals.com. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to FindRentals.com and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL: <http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html>

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include Google Adsense. These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on FindRentals.com send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see. FindRentals.com has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers. 

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. FindRentals.com's privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites. If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers' respective websites. 

**Questions and comments?**

The FindRentals.com Customer Privacy Policy has been developed out of respect for the privacy preferences and choices of our customers and prospects. We have established procedures to ensure that every reasonable effort is made to address your concerns. Each business unit within FindRentals.com has designated a Privacy Official to implement our Customer Privacy Policy for its respective customers and prospects. You should find contact information on each of our business unit's Web sites that collect data from you.
